SALIH KHAN

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full stack freelance developer with 3 years experience in Vue.js. and 1 year experience in NodeJS. Developed complete frontend applications with integrations to backend following best practises and security protocols. Fluent in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and extensive experience in firebase storage/firestore and MongoDB and in using MEVN (MongoDB, Express, Vuejs, NodeJS) tech stack. Quick learner and creative in design and implementation and very practical at server-side development following industry standard.

WORK HISTORY

Assistant Postmaster, 06/2023 to Current Williams Road Post Office - Burnley, Lancashire

- Sorted and 10+ differentiated types of packages into categories and types.
- Offered flexible hours to provide additional support in busy holiday periods, whilst keeping employee and customer area organised/clean
- Followed security policies to prevent work mishaps.
- Sorted 5 receipts daily into sorted folders for administrative purposes.

Freelance web developer, 07/2022 to Current Self-Employed - Burnley, Lancashire

- Utilised MEVN tech-stack for development
- · Performed/maintained hundreds of data-entry into Mongo database
- Developed application from client requirements with MVC structure and best security practises
- Applied responsive design across multiple devices for 100% compatibility.

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- · Physics simulation
- Games development in C++
- Arduino projects (micro-controllers)
- · Light gaming (sandbox, strategy and creative)
- · Reading fiction and fantasy
- Languages

CERTIFICATIONS

Sololearn: HTML, CSS, JS, C#, C++ Udemy: Node.js, Vue.js

CONTACT

Address: 10 Board Street, Burnley,

Lancashire BB10 1JN **Phone:** 07440290893

Email: salihkhan1701@gmail.com

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

https://salihkhan.me

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Node.js
- Vue.js
- Database management and integration
- · Git/GitHub
- Full stack management
- · Search Engine Optimisation
- UX and UI

EDUCATION

NVQ Level 3, Computing, 09/2022 to 05/2024

Burnley College - Burnley

· Graduated with DDD

GCSEs, 09/2017 to 08/2018 Sir John Thursby Community

College - Burnley, Lancashire

Computer Science: 6

History: 5

Mathematics: 5

German: 5

English Literature: 4 English Language: 5

Combined sciences: Trilogy: 5-5